那是德州东部一个美好的早晨
It was a beautiful morning in East Texas.
是那种令你想起床
The kind of morning that made you want to get up,
穿好衣服  测试重力加速度
get dressed and test that acceleration due to gravity
并不受物体的移动影响的早晨
does not depend on an object's motion.
我好爱周六啊
I love Saturdays.
地球对任何物体都是施加相同的重力加速度
The Earth causes the same gravitational acceleration of everything,
无论你是手办还是乒乓球
even a doll and a flying Ping-Pong ball.
科学界的人
It's not often a man of science
很少真心实意说出"流弊啊"  但...
gets to say "Yippee ki-yay," and mean it, but...
流弊啊
Yippee ki-yay.
早啊  赫谢尔
Morning, Herschel.
乔治  你没看到有只狗
Hey, George. Uh, you didn't see a dog
跑来你家这溜达吧
wandering around here, did you?
没啊  你们养狗啦
No. Y'all get a dog?
算吧  我大舅子要搬去有栅栏社区
Uh, sort of. We took him in after my brother-in-law
我们就收养了这条狗
had to go live in a gated community.
感觉不错啊  他们那里禁养宠物吗
Oh, that sounds nice; uh, they got a no pets policy?
是去坐牢  乔治
He's in jail, George.
好吧  行
Right, sure.
物理学里  没有什么比预测出结果的感觉更棒了
In physics, nothing feels better than predicting an outcome.
我爱可预测性
I love predictability.
重力  可预测
The force of gravity: predictable.
核聚变  可预测
Nuclear fusion: predictable.
我哥在淋浴间里撒尿
My brother peeing in the shower:
很恶心  但可预测
repulsive, but predictable.
那什么不可预测呢
What isn't predictable:
狗
dogs.
我一直都很害怕狗
I've always been terrified of dogs.
对我来说它们就是个毛绒绒的庞大问号
To me, they're nothing but big, furry question marks.
长了牙的问号
Question marks with teeth.
在惊慌的时刻  我常常失去知觉
In panic situations, I'd often lose consciousness.
而这次  我只失去了声音
This time, I only lost my voice.
救命
Help.
快救命啊
Please help.
♪ 世上没人比我强壮 ♪
♪ Nobody else is stronger than I am ♪
♪ 昨天我移了一座山 ♪
♪ Yesterday I moved a mountain ♪
♪ 我相信我能当你的英雄 ♪
♪ I bet I could be your hero ♪
♪ 我是个了不起的小家伙 ♪
♪ I am a mighty little man ♪
少
年
谢尔顿
我只是在欣赏
Uh, I was just admiring
蓝爷爷独特的拐杖
Grandpa Smurf's unique walking stick.
蓝精灵哟喂呀
Smurf-a-loo-loo.
那不是我的拐杖
That's not my walking stick.
午餐好了
Lunch is ready.
你能去叫你弟弟来吃饭吗
Can you go get your brother?
我在看电视呢
I'm watching TV.
快去
Just go.
这家里什么都他蓝精灵的要我干
I have to do smurfing everything around here.
我听到了
I heard that.
我说的是"他蓝精灵"
I said "smurfing."
我听到了你用这词的方式
And I heard how you said it.
她自己给自己吐司切边吧
She can cut her own crusts off.
谢尔顿
Sheldon?
你是谁呀
Who are you?
你真可爱
You're so cute.
小心点
Be careful.
你躲在那上面干嘛
What are you doing up there?
保护性命
Staying alive.
这是谁的狗啊
Whose dog is this?
我不知道  快叫人来救命
I don't know. Get help.
它怎么进我们车库的
Well, how did he get into the garage?
快请你去找人来救命
Please get help.
或许我们可以收养它
Maybe we can keep it.
我求你了  快去找人来
I'm begging you, get help now.
首先  我得告诉你一件事
First, I have to tell you something.
什么
What?
午餐好了
Lunch is ready.
你看看
Will you look at that?
什么狗会咬穿木头啊
What kind of dog chews through wood?
你们都有喂它吧
Y'all are feeding him, right?
或许它是在磨牙
Maybe he's teething.
比利小的时候
You know, when Billy was little,
他咬穿了他的围栏
he chewed right through his playpen.
-真的假的  -他只有三颗牙
- No kidding? - Only had three teeth.
基本都是靠牙龈咬的
Mostly gummed it.
所以你们打算怎么处理
So how y'all want to fix it?
我想我可以把这里补上
Well, I figure I'll patch it,
然后用细铁丝网围住下面这块
run some chicken wire along the bottom--
这样它就不能再来咬穿个洞了
that way, he don't chew through it again.
你们好
Hello.
-你好  -你好啊  比利
- Hey. - ‭Hey, Billy.
以前这里就有个围栏窗口了吗
Was this fence window always here?
不是的儿子  这围栏窗口是新的
No, son, that's a new fence window.
有人感觉头晕吗
Anybody else getting dizzy?
你怎么不叫人救你呢
Why didn't you call for help?
我试过了  但我发不出声音
I tried, but no sound came out.
可怜的孩子
You poor thing.
车库上面好脏啊
It was very dirty up there.
打扫车库是你还是爸爸的责任
Is cleaning the garage your job or Dad's?
你不用担心那个
Don't you worry about that.
来  喝点茶
Here, have some tea.
-甘菊茶吗  -是的
- Chamomile? ‭- Yes.
加一茶匙的蜂蜜了吗
One teaspoon of honey?
加了
Yes.
加了一块冰块来降温了吗
An ice cube to cool it off?
我给你加了两块
I went with two today.
你今天过得太惨了
You've been through enough.
我还是比较喜欢加一块冰
I prefer one ice cube.
快给老娘喝了
Drink it.
孩子们都上床了之后真好
It's nice when the kids are in bed,
我们可以就在这放松聚着
and we can just hang out and relax.
你这话我连回都懒得回
I'm not even gonna respond to that.
终于把他哄睡了
I finally got him asleep.
他现在还惊魂未定
He's still pretty shook up.
或许隔壁养这条狗也不是什么坏事
Maybe having this mutt next door won't be so bad.
谢利说不定哪天就能习惯了
Shelly could end up getting used to it.
这倒是真的
That's true.
还记得他以前总因为
Remember when he got all freaked out
酸奶底下的水果而小题大做吗
by the fruit at the bottom of yogurt?
他现在也能正常吃了
Now he eats it no problem.
他现在也还是要我帮他搅好啊
He still makes me stir it.
或许他可以一步步来
Maybe you could start out
先从小动物开始  再慢慢适应大的
with a small pet, and work your way up.
比如小乌龟
Like a turtle.
他说乌龟带有沙门氏菌
He says they carry salmonella.
沙鼠呢
A gerbil?
黑死病的真正元凶好像是它们
Apparently, they caused the plague.
那鸟呢
What about a bird?
这题我来答
Oh, I know that one.
它们会偷他的头发去筑巢
They'll steal his hair to make a nest.
妈
Mom!
至少这次我能发出声音了
At least this time, sound came out.
我觉得这算是进步
I call that progress.
怎么了
What's going on?
你家的狗跑进我家里了
Your dog got into our house.
它怎么进去的
How the hell did he do that?
它把纱窗给推开了
He pushed in a screen window.
你觉得它是不是又把围栏咬穿了
You think he chewed through the fence again?
我只知道谢尔顿对着这狗吼
All I know is Sheldon's yelling at the dog,
然后玛丽就吼我
and Mary's yelling at me.
而我现在在这看着你穿着内裤
Now I'm looking at you in your underwear.
要命了  赫谢尔  怎么了
Damn it, Herschel, what is going on?
你好啊  乔治
Oh, hey, George.
你好啊  布兰达
Hey, Brenda.
巴基跑进他们家里了
Bucky got in their house.
这还挺好笑
That's funny.
或许哪天回忆起来挺好笑  但现在不好笑
It might be funny one day, not right now.
真的很抱歉啦  乔治
Look, I'm real sorry, George.
我会把它拴上  下次不会这样了
I'll keep him tied up, it won't happen again.
你们晚安
Y'all have a good night.
乔治
George!
你绝对不敢相信  你看
You are not gonna believe this. Look.
他们的狗留了一只死松鼠在我们客厅
Their dog left a dead squirrel in our living room.
它有猎狗的血统
Well, h-he is part hunting dog.
我想这表示它喜欢你们
I think that means he likes you.
我对它的喜爱没有兴趣
I'm not interested in winning his affection.
我只对不让狗与啮齿动物进我家有兴趣
I'm interested in keeping dogs and rodents outside of my home.
等等
Well, now, hold on.
你怎么知道是巴基
How do we know it was Bucky that left
把这只松鼠留在你家的
that squirrel in your house?
或许这松鼠本来就在那里了啊
Maybe that squirrel was already there.
除了它  我家客厅怎么可能会有死松鼠
Why else would a dead squirrel be in my living room?
我哪知道你怎么打理你家的
I don't know what kind of house you keep.
我家一尘不染
My house is immaculate.
乔治  你告诉他们
George, tell them. ‭Uh...
他的确把家里打理得很好
She does keep a nice house.
亲爱的  的确很可能是巴基留下的
Honey, it's a pretty good chance it was Bucky.
-你站谁那边  -你的  永远你这边
- Whose side are you on? - Yours, always yours.
好啦  现在大家情绪都不好  时间也晚了
All right. Everyone's upset, it's late.
我们今晚这事就先缓缓吧
Maybe we should drop this for tonight?
好主意  好啦
That's a good idea. Okay.
你把你家狗关得离我儿子远点
You just keep your dog away from my son.
-你又重启战火啦  -抱歉
- There you go picking it up again. - I am sorry,
但是他们家的狗偷闯进我们家
but their dog broke into our home.
或许是跟她哥哥学的
Something he probably learned from your brother.
你好大的胆子
How dare you.
好了  我觉得在这里停下挺好的
Okay, I think that's a good stopping point.
我们怎么知道不是你儿子
How do we know that your son didn't
引诱巴基  想在狗身上做什么奇怪的科学实验
lure Bucky in to perform weird science experiments on him?
我儿子当时已经上床睡了  你好大的胆子...
My son was asleep in his bed, and you have some nerve...
晚安啦  乔治
Night, George!
晚安
Night!
我真不懂那条狗
I don't understand why that dog
对谢尔顿这么感兴趣
is so interested in Sheldon.
或许巴基喜欢谢尔顿的味道
Maybe Bucky likes the way Sheldon smells?
你弟弟一天洗三次澡
Your brother washes himself three times a day.
他没有味道
He has no smell.
找到了  动物管理局
Here we go: animal control.
别  别
Oh, no, no.
不行  你怎么可以打给动物管理局呢
No, you don't want to go calling animal control.
-为什么不行  -因为
- Why not? - ‭Because,
你还得住在这些人的隔壁呢
you have to live next door to these people.
小乔治音乐放太大声他们也打给警察了啊
They called the cops on Georgie when he played music too loud.
或许是他们  也可能是我
Maybe it was them, maybe it was me.
但重点是
Anyway, the point is,
你想灭火就不能火上浇油啊
you don't can't go throwing gasoline on the fire.
是他们自己放的火
Well, they started this fire,
现在准备引火自焚吧
and now, they're gonna get burned.
我觉得你咖啡喝够多了  再喝上脑
I believe you've had enough coffee.
我说  要不你让我去跟布兰达谈吧
Listen, why don't you let me talk to Brenda,
让我来摆平这件事
and just smooth things out?
你凭什么觉得她会听你的话
Why do you think she'll listen to you?
因为人们喜欢我多过喜欢你啊
Because people like me more than you.
大家喜欢我啊
People like me.
我没说别人不喜欢你  只说更喜欢我
I didn't say they don't, they just like me more.
总之  我整天在保龄球馆遇见她
Anyway, I see her all the time at bowling.
我知道怎么跟她相处
I know how to handle her.
行
Fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
很多人都喜欢我好吗
Plenty of people like me.
布兰达  最近好吗
Hey, Brenda, how's it going?
你女儿烦人得要死  你说好不好
Your daughter's a pain in my ass, that's how it's going.
你还真是明人不说暗话啊
You don't beat around the bush.
我一直都喜欢你这点
I've always liked that about you.
康妮  我今晚上班够累了
Connie, I've had a long night.
除非你是想打球  不然我懒得听你废话
Unless you're looking to bowl, I don't want to hear it.
来嘛  别这样
Aw, now, come on.
让我请你喝杯酒  咱们来聊两句
Let me buy you a drink, and we'll talk about this.
我比你想象中更支持你呢
I'm more on your side than you think.
-我莫名不太敢信呢  -是真的
- Somehow, i doubt that. - ‭It's true.
你以为我就没觉得玛丽有时候是个...
Don't you think I realize that Mary can be a bit...
自以为是的臭婊子吗
Of a self-righteous bitch?
我本来要说"难相处"  但你这么说也可以
I was gonna say "challenging," but sure, let's go with yours.
说起来挺顺口的
It's got a nice rhythm.
布兰达  这不得不说
Brenda, this is, by far,
是我们这里保龄球馆中最好喝的玛格丽塔了
the best bowling alley margarita in town.
你跟赫谢尔结婚多少年了  18  19年了吗
How long you and Herschel been married? 18, 19 years?
19年  感觉像30年了
19, but it feels like 30.
你们也算是神仙眷侣啦
Well, y'all are a great couple.
我是想谢谢你
I just wanted to thank you
从我女儿跟她一家人搬过来之后
for being so patient and kind to my daughter and her family
就对他们包容又友善
since they moved in.
-这没什么  -不  我得说出来
- It's nothing. - ‭No, it needs to be said.
玛丽养育那三个孩子很不容易
You know, Mary has a tough job raising those three kids,
尤其其中一个还挺...特别的
with one of them being, you know, somewhat special.
-我看得出  -是啊
- I can see that. ‭- Yeah.
有友善的邻居让一切都好多了
And having a kind neighbor makes all the difference in the world.
我们尽力而为
Well, we try.
我知道你也很清楚压力有多大
And I know you know how stressful it is,
因为你也有一个
seeing as how you have your own child
很特别的儿子
who is special in his own way.
这话是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
我知道比利是个很棒的孩子
Well, I mean, hey, I know Billy is a terrific little boy,
但他一定给你和赫谢尔带来过
but I am sure he has presented you and Herschel
不少挑战
with some challenges.
要说我们这区有哪个孩子怪异
If there's a weird kid in the neighborhood,
一定是你的外孙
it's your grandson.
等一下  我说的是"特别"  不是"怪异"
Now, hang on, I said "special," not "weird."
我听到了
I heard you.
我说的是"怪异"
I said "weird."
知道吗  布兰达
Okay, see now, Brenda,
劝你不要说我外孙"怪异"
you don't want to go calling my grandson weird
因为我刚刚才请你喝了玛格丽塔酒
when I've just treated you to a margarita grande.
不好意思  但你也不该暗示
Well, I'm sorry, but you shouldn't be inferring
我家比利有毛病
there's something wrong with my Billy.
亲  这不是暗示
Darlin', there's no inferring.
我见过你儿子坐在泥地上
I've seen the boy sitting in the dirt
吃他肚脐里的棉絮团
eating his own belly button lint.
真的吗  妈妈  你就是这样灭火的
Really, Mom? This is how you put out the fire?
至少她伤得比较重
Well, at least she got the worst of it.
你怎么得出这结论的
How you figure that?
我把她一大片头发给扯下来了
I ripped a big patch of hair out of her head.
这淤青一周就会好
This will be healed in a week.
而她到劳动节前都得戴帽子遮丑
She will be wearing a hat till Labor Day.
我长大后要像你一样
I want to be just like you when I grow up.
-不行  -三思啊
- No, you don't. - ‭Pick again.
请问一下  哈钦斯老师
Excuse me, Ms. Hutchins?
谢尔顿好啊
Hey, Sheldon.
你能推荐克服恐惧的书吗
Can you recommend any books on overcoming phobias?
那些都在自助书籍区
That's in the self-help section.
跟我来  我全都看过
Follow me, I have read them all.
-有特指哪种恐惧吗  -狗
- Any phobia in particular? ‭- Dogs.
恐犬病  这个不错
Ah, cynophobia. That's a good one.
你知道光在美国
Did you know there's over 50 million dogs
就有超过5千万只狗吗
just in the United States alone?
多余了5千万只狗
That's 50 million too many.
给  我读这本来改善我的接触恐惧症
Here. I read this one to help with my haphephobia.
害怕被碰触  我也有这病症  有用吗
Ah, fear of being touched. I have that, too. Was it useful?
等有人有兴趣碰我时
Well, when someone's interested in touching me,
就知道了
we'll find out.
这本书的基本前提是
The basic premise of the book was that phobias
想克服恐惧
were overcome by taking incremental steps
必须逐步面对该恐惧
toward confronting the phobia in question.
对我而言  就是从看一个
In my case, that started with watching a TV show
全天下小朋友都喜欢
that was adored by children around the world,
但于我如同噩梦的电视节目开始
but for me, was the stuff of nightmares.
史酷比
Scooby-Doo!
下一步就是跟真正的狗
The next step was to go face-to-face
面对面
with real dogs.
虽然是透过一扇玻璃窗
Albeit through a plate-glass window.
够了够了
Okay, that's enough.
最后
And finally,
第三种近距离接触
a close encounter of the third kind,
与一种犬科动物进行身体接触
physical contact with a member of the canine species.
你好  我想找兽医
Hello, I'd like to speak with the veterinarian.
我希望你有一两只处于麻醉状态的狗
Well, I was hoping you might have one or two dogs
能让我来摸一下
under anesthesia that I might come by and pet.
好的  我等着
Sure, I'll hold.
你在跟谁打电话
Who are you talking to?
梅福德兽医诊所
The Medford Veterinary Clinic.
为什么
Why?
我想克服我对狗的恐惧
I'm trying to overcome my fear of dogs
不然我们家还得受更大影响
before it affects our family any further.
宝贝  你不必担心我们会受影响
Oh, honey, you don't have to worry about how it affects us.
姥姥脸上被揍了一拳  都是因为我
Meemaw got punched in the face because of me.
不  那不是你造成的  再说了
No, that wasn't because of you, and for the record,
你姥姥脸上经常挨揍啊
your meemaw gets punched in the face all the time.
我仍然认为我需要
Well, I still think I need to take
采取一些积极行动
some sort of positive action.
-喂  -喂  你好
- Hello? - Yes, hello?
真不幸
Oh, that's too bad.
那有最近老死的蓬毛小型犬吗
How about a small fluffy one that's recently died of old age?
够了
Enough.
抱歉
Sorry.
《马可福音》12章31节说到
Now, it says here in Mark 12:31
"要爱邻如己"
that you should "Love your neighbor as yourself."
有人想猜猜这是什么意思吗  米希
Anybody like to take a guess what that means? Missy?
意思是要对邻居友善
It means to be nice to the people who live next door.
没错
That's right.
至于剩下的人就都下地狱去吧
But everybody else can go to hell.
米希  我们这儿不能说这种话
Okay, Missy, we don't use that kind of language here.
如果仔细想想  在现在这个时代
And if you think about it, in this world,
我们有那么多旅行方式  所有人都是你的邻居
with all the ways we can travel, everybody's your neighbor.
谢尔顿
Yes, Sheldon.
我们的妈妈互相讨厌
How do we love our neighbors
我们又如何爱自己的邻居呢
when our moms hate each other?
-你妈妈讨厌谁  -你妈妈
- Who does your mom hate? - Your mom.
我妈妈也讨厌你妈妈  好巧哦
Hey, my mom hates your mom. Small world.
好了  先等一下
Okay, let's hang on a second.
我妈妈也讨厌他们的姥姥
My mom also hates their grandma.
因为她打架输给她了
'Cause she lost a fight to her.
才不  她赢了  她说的
Nuh-uh, she won. She said so.
好了  都别说了
All right, stop. Let's stop.
这也许难以理解
Now this might be hard to understand,
但过充满爱的基督徒生活
but living a loving, Christian life
并非易事
isn't always the easiest thing to do.
比利
Yes, Billy.
我妈妈也不太喜欢你
My mom's not crazy about you either.
爱你们的邻居  好吗
Just love your neighbor, 'kay?
我的教区居民之间关系不好
Now, I am more than willing to look the other way
我很愿意睁只眼闭只眼
when my parishioners don't get along with each other.
这是常有的事  但如果问题影响到孩子
That sort of thing happens, but when it becomes a problem
我就得插手了
for the children, then I have to intervene.
根本没问题
There's no problem here,
只除了这俩人觉得自己比我强
other than these two thinking that they're better than me.
我不是觉得  我知道
I don't think it, I know it.
我狠揍了你妈一顿
I gave your mother a good smacking.
我也可以让你尝尝厉害
I can give you one, too.
头发横着梳掩饰秃头的人也好意思说
That's big talk from somebody with a comb-over.
女士们
Ladies.
我需要提醒你们  我们都是基督徒吗
Do I need to remind you that we are Christians?
在我们所有的行为行动中
In all our behavior, in all our actions,
我们都必须不断扪心自问
we must constantly ask ourselves the question,
"耶稣会怎么做"
"What would Jesus do?"
我能说几句吗
Can I say something?
耶稣会说那些吗
Would Jesus say it?
算了
Never mind.
在我人生中
In my life,
我常被说是行动上的懦夫
I've often been accused of being a physical coward,
大部分时候  这说法是对的
and for the most part, those accusations are correct.
但我也曾数次表现出巨大的勇气
But there have been times when I've shown great courage.
这就是其中一次
This was one of them.
巴基你好啊
Hello, Bucky.
你是乖狗狗吗
Are you a good dog?
拜托你乖乖的
Please be a good dog.
拜托了
Please.
很多时候  我们不喜欢别人
Now oftentimes, when we don't like someone,
是因为看到他们身上有我们自身也有
what's happening is we see something in them
且不喜欢的的缺点
that we don't like in ourselves.
你在说什么
What are you saying?
不是吧  你这都听不懂
Really? That was over your head?
我是说
I'm saying,
你们也许比想象中有更多共同点
y'all might have more in common than you think.
千万别说他们的孩子都很"特别"
Well, don't say both their kids are "special."
她可不喜欢听这话
She does not like that.
好吧
Okay.
来吧
Here we go.
抚摸...狗狗
Petting... the dog.
我做到了
I'm doing it.
我在摸狗狗
I'm petting a dog.
我战胜了我的恐惧
I've conquered my phobia.
你是只乖狗狗  你就是
You're a good boy. Yes, you are.
抱歉我对你说了那些恶毒话
I'm sorry for the unkind things I said to you.
我也是
Me, too.
康妮
Connie?
干嘛
What?
你有话想说吗
Anything you'd like to say?
并没有
Not particularly.
妈妈
Mom.
好吧
Okay.
抱歉我说了那些话
I'm sorry for the things I said,
在保龄球馆发生的事我也很抱歉
and, you know, what happened at the bowling alley.
我也是
As am I.
给
Here.
这应该是从你脑袋上掉下来的
I think this came out of your head.
它舔了我  它舔了我
He licked me! He licked me!
那只狗舔了我的舌头
The dog licked my tongue!
我嘴里还有那个味道
I can still taste it!
快打急救电话
Call 911!
耶稣应该会去看看什么情况
I think Jesus might go check that out.
你在里面怎么样了  宝贝
How's it going in there, baby?
还行  但家里需要再买漱口水了
Okay, but we're gonna need more Listerine.
他试图克服恐狗症  我很骄傲
I'm proud of him for trying to overcome that damn dog phobia.
你应该告诉他啊
You should tell him that.
如果他从浴室出来  我会说的
Well, if he ever leaves that bathroom, I will.
我想不明白的是  那只狗为何这么喜欢谢尔顿
What I can't figure out is why that dog is so drawn to Sheldon.
问倒我了
Beats me.
-你说它的主人进监狱了对吗  -是的
- You say his owner's in the slammer? ‭- Yeah.
不知道他是什么样的人
Wonder what kind of fella he is.
百利牌发胶
真是个谜
It's a mystery.
恐怕我们永远都不会知道
I guess we'll never know.
小饼饼
Hey, Moonpie.
我带了样东西
I got you a little something to help you
帮你克服对动物的恐惧
get over your fear of animals.
麻醉枪吗
A tranquilizer gun?
是一条宠物鱼
A pet fish.
{\an8\fn@方正兰亭特黑_GBK\fs30\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H000000&\frz270\fs40\pos(55.431,132.717)}《鱼·库珀简史》
为什么
Why?
我想着你可以从小的开始  循序渐进
Well, I thought you could start small and then work your way up.
瞧  它挺可爱的
Look, he's kind of cute.
它对我的存在毫不在意  我喜欢它
He doesn't even care that I'm here. I like him.
你打算叫它什么
What are you gonna name him?
鱼
Fish.
鱼吗
Fish?
我还没准备好产生感情
I'm not ready to get attached.
鱼有点无聊
Fish are kind of boring.
我知道  太棒了不是吗
I know, isn't it great?
但连摸都不能摸
But you can't even pet 'em.
也许可以呢
Maybe we can.
宝贝  出什么事了
Baby, what's wrong?
我试着抚摸鱼  它身体好黏滑
I tried to pet Fish! Ah, he was so slimy!
鱼就是这样的
Well, yeah, he's a fish.
我把手指伸进鱼缸  然后我碰了它
I put my finger in the top of the tank, then I touched him,
结果它咬我
and he bit me!
它肯定没有咬你啦
Oh, I'm sure he didn't bite you.
我无法呼吸了
I can't breathe.
它的鱼血现在跟我的人血混在一起了
His fish blood is mixing with my human blood.
-也许它只是想亲你呢  -不
- Maybe he was just trying to give you a kiss. - ‭No.
它讨厌我  我再也不想看到它
He hates me. I never want to see him again.
谢尔顿  别犯傻了
Oh, Sheldon, you're being silly.
这种小鱼不会咬人
Fish like this don't bite.
你瞧  毫无杀伤力
Look. See? He's harmless.
妈了个逼
Son of a bitch!
爸爸杀了我的鱼
Dad killed my fish!
乔治
George!
它不会有事的
He'll be fine.
把它放回缸里就好了
Just got to put him back in the bowl.
乔治
Oh, George.
完结